

DAVANN TEM

MANAGEMENT ASSISTANT



+358 45 787 222 83 @davanntem



temdavann@gmail.com Sokinsuonkuja 1 B13 02760 Espoo

EDUCATION

B.A. Multilingual Management Assistants Haaga-Helia UAS | Aug 2016 - Dec 2019

Erasmus Exchange Programme European University of Madrid | Jan - Jun 2017

B.A. English for Professional Communication Royal University of Phnom Penh | 2009 - 2013

WORK EXPERIENCE

Logrus Ry

Marketing & PR Intern | Jan-March 2021

- Plan and manage social media marketing for Musical Theater Festival Helsinki
- Connect with international communities to promote the festival
- Provide customer service at the audition

Unfair Advantage Oy

Part-time Digital Marketing Assistant | Nov-Dec 2020

- Creating marketing materials and office documents
- Planning and managing social media marketing

DenconFoods Oy

Sales & Marketing Assistant Intern | Sep 2018-Jan 2019

- Part of maintaining & adjusting product specifications in the database.
- Together with team setting up a new company presentation & social media presence using different social media tools
- Assisting sales and marketing team with setting up new POS materials.

KPMG Cambodia Ltd.

Tax Consultant | Oct 2013 - Apr 2015

- Preparing and processing documents for monthly and annual tax declaration, tax registration and company dissolution notification for clients' companies to the Tax Office.
- Preparing draft tax advisory and proposals to clients
- Performing other administrative tasks & customer services.

PERSONAL PROFILE

A diligent and self-motivated management assistant specialized in marketing, sales and services.

My previous working experiences have given me the ability to work independently and in team with multi-nationality, proven my ability to work under pressure with detail and result orientation.

My ambition is to succeed in a stimulating and challenging environment, bring the upto-date knowledge and skills to build the success of the company while I experience advancement opportunities.

SKILLS

Microsoft Office Social Media Marketing **ERP System CRM System** Adobe Premiere Pro

LANGUAGES

Khmer - Mother tongue

English - Excellent

Finnish - Intermediate (Yki taso 3)

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Cambodia Essay Contest For young People

Core team member | Oct 2020-Now

Arctic15

Building-up team | June 2019

Badge-claim team | December 2017

NewCo Helsinki

Event assistant | October 2017